Ajay said
yes yes if there is no need then one should not go out at all.
By the way I am thinking that if we do
not want to hide here for 3 months then this loan waiver is
not there after the expiry of the period, then this loan will be waived from the nearby shop along with
onions. But if we are getting this
facility now then
what is the harm in taking advantage of it friends this is
for those people whose interest has gone
or reduced due to age, if we can pay regularly then
we should pay because this means this
increase in the loan, understand if you have
taken a loan at 10 percent interest and your
monthly interest is Rs. 25000, suppose you have to
pay for 216 months and you are 3
months old, after the moratorium ends
you will have to pay Rs. 233 instead of 216, that is a
total of 17,
how did it increase so much by taking a moratorium of 3 months, by
taking a break in 3 months,
compound interest will be charged on it which will be
added to your principal amount
and your interest will increase a lot,
I never thought of this, my
income is anyway regular, I am not taking this moratorium  I will
not take it at all because it is in our
instead, meaning it has increased in May